<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="realaxxxx/homeworkShema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<root>
    <info>
        <title>ingydar</title>
        <person type="artist">Adrianne Lenker</person>
        <label>Producers </label>
        <producer>
            <person type="producer">Phil Weinrobe</person>
         
            <person type="producer">Adrianne Lenker</person>
        </producer>
        <location>Track 2 on <album>songs</album></location>
        <date when="2020-10-23">Oct. 23, 2020</date>
        <views>
            <num n="115,100">115.1K</num>
            <unit>views</unit>
        </views>
    </info>

    <lyrics>
        <verse n="1">
            <line>Fragilely, gradually and surrounding</line>
            <line>The horse lies naked in the shed</line>
            <line>Evergreen anodyne decompounding</line>
            <line>Flies draw sugar from his head</line>
        </verse>


        <preChorus>
            <line>His eyes are blueberries, video screens, Minneapolis schemes</line>
            <line>And the dried flowers from books half-read</line>
            <line>The juice of dark cherries cover his chin</line>
            <line>The dog walks in and the crow lies in his jaw like lead</line>
        </preChorus>

        <chorus>
            <line>Everything eats and is eaten Time is fed</line>
        </chorus>

        <verse n="2">
            <line>Early еvening, the pink ring swallows</line>
            <line>The sphеrical marigold terrain</line>
            <line>Sleepily, Venus sinks and hollows</line>
            <line>The stationed headlight of a plane</line>
        </verse>
        <!--[Pre-Chorus]-->
        <preChorus>
            <line>You are as far from me as memory</line>
            <line>With fixtures fracture varyingly</line>
            <line>The juice of dark cherries cover my skin</line>
            <line>Six years in, no baby</line>
        </preChorus>




        <chorus>
            <line>Everything eats and is eaten</line>
        </chorus>


        <verse n="3">
            <line>Ingydar bares a scar like a meteor</line>
            <line>Crystalline amber guilds her cheek</line>
            <line>Tambourine of the beech leaves lead her</line>
            <line>To the raven playing hide and seek</line>
        </verse>


        <preChorus>
            <line>Drying blueberries, figurines</line>
            <line>And the angel leans at the head of the bed</line>
            <line>The juice of dark cherries cover her chin</line>
            <line>The dog walks in and the crow lies in his smile like lead</line>
        </preChorus>


        <chorus>
            <line>Everything eats and is eaten, time is fed</line>
            <line>Everything eats and is eaten</line>
            <line>Everything eats and is eaten</line>
            <line>Everything eats and is eaten</line>
            <line>Everything eats and is eaten</line>
            <line>Everything eats and is eaten</line>
        </chorus>
    </lyrics>

    <about><label>About</label> For <company>GQ</company>, <person type="artist">Lenker</person>
        said: Ingydar was the name of my great-aunt Becky’s horse, who passed away when I was a kid.
        But the song itself, I have to say, it isn’t really about that horse. That was just a
        fragment from the pool of ideas, or colors that I wove into the song, but yeah. “Everything
        eats and is eaten / Time is fed.” Have you ever used a vacuum cleaner, and there’s a button
        that sucks the cord back in? I imagine life being like the cord, and just being sucked back
        into the mouth of time, or that time is built up of experience in life. I suppose this is a
        pretty common thing to think about and philosophize about, but just looking at it as
        nonlinear, and as like a big orb or sphere, or maybe shapeless, but not with a before and an
        after and like a linear trajectory, but actually cyclical. Everything is constantly being
        born and decaying simultaneously. We’re both growing and becoming, and also unbecoming and
        decaying simultaneously. It’s like there’s this inherent duality within everything. I was
        going through a transition in a relationship at the time that was so painful and still is,
        but that feeling of our relationship just being eaten, or the idea of like, whatever state
        we’re in now, me and this person that were in this relationship, it’s our relationship, and
        all the journey and processing we had to go through was the sacrifice for our new state of
        being. And it was eaten by time.</about>
</root>
